[{"answer": "So, what do you think", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "About the opera", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "About the opera", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "You gotta go", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Nah, I don't wanna go", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Oh come on my friend, its opening night, black tie, Pagliacci! The great clown, the great sad tragic clown, like you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Oh, well I have many associates", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Well I guess if I'm the Miana I should go. All right, all right. my friend ENTER", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Hi", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Well I'm looking forward to meeting him", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Where are you going, what's the rush", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I've got to g", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I'm going to surprise my friend, I've never been to his apartment so I'm just going to 'pop in", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "OK Quiet! Quiet! Now let me think", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "The cops? What are you calling the cops for? They're not going to do anything", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I'm gonna call the cops. That's what I'm doing, I'm calling the cops", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "What do you mean they're not going to do anything, they're the cops, they gotta do something, he just put the kibosh on me, do you know what the kibosh means, its a kibosh", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I mean it's a terrible mistake, I mean he thinks I ruined some deal of his at that place, I don't know anything about any deal at that place", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "That's what I'll do, I'll just call him and tell him, I'll tell him. That's all I'll do. He's a human being, I'll talk to him. He'll understand. Right", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Call him and tell hi", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Right.... Don't mention my nam", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Oh, nothing, I just stopped by to chat, you know, shoot the breeze", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Oh, no, he couldn't get them. We're not going", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Do you know the last time I wore this thing? Six years ago, when I made that toast at my friend's wedding", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "It wasn't that bad", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Well it is mine", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "You think I care about money, that's how much I care about money, I don't care about money", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "You think I care about money, that's how much I care about money, I don't care about money", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Why don't you get lost", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I got two, I got two huh, Paliachi, who needs two, my friend, come on, the great tragic clown, come on, check it out, he laughs, he cries, he sings, my friend. Hey, I got two beauties right here, check it out all right", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Oh yeah, I'm selling", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah, when my friend made that bad toast", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Oh yeah, the curse toast", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Crazy my frien", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "What do you mean? Why wouldn't I know his name", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "How do you know his name", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I never told you his name", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "What do you mean? Why wouldn't I know his name", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I never told you his name", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Oh my god, its my frien", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "That madman is trying to kill me", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Hey pop, would you buzz off, I've got something cooking", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Mr my friend", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Two fifty", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Yeah, yeah, I'm sure", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "So what, they don't have another plane? She couldn't take a bus", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Yeah you made it, how about that", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "These are great seats huh", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Yea", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Boy, some cast, huh? my friend, my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Opera.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "She's playing, my friend's wife, my friend", "qsentId": 52}]